Believe in the magic of music.
The Magic Flute is a adventure, fantasy, music film directed by Florian Sigl.
A seventeen year old travels from London to the Austrian Alps
to attend the legendary Mozart boarding school.
There, he discovers a centuries-old forgotten passageway into the
fantastic world of Mozart's "The Magic Flute".
Tim Walker / Prince Tamino, played by Jack Wolfe.
Dr. Longbow, played by F. Murray Abraham.
Sophie Longbow, played by Niamh McCormack.
Paolo Tocci (as Elliot Courtiour), played by Ellie Courtiour.
Olivia, played by Cosima Henman.
Anton Milanesi, played by Amir Wilson.
The Magic Flute (German: The Magic Flute - Das Vermächtnis der Zauberflöte) is a 2022 German musical fantasy film directed by Florian Sigl
and written by Andrew Lowery, based on the 1791 opera of the same name by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart and Emanuel Schikaneder.
The film explores themes of london, england, magic,
boarding school, musical, mozart.